日常工作
翻译：桃了  压制：感康小快客
校对 & 后期：@Phuckq
甜蜜兴奋剂
【三次元成瘾者康复中心】倾情奉献
更多动画 新浪@Kresent
本字幕仅供学习交流 严禁用于商业用途
好吧 因为帕布觉得你们已经能够承担更多责任了
Alright. Because Pops thinks you're ready for more responsibility,
他希望我给你们分配一些更重要的工作
he wants me to give you more important jobs.
那么你们就从准备早会的甜甜圈开始吧
So I'm gonna start by having you get the donuts for the morning meeting.
真的吗
Whoa, really?
对 但首先 听清楚规则
Yes. But first, some ground rules.
一 帮我买个全麦甜甜圈
One, pick me up a whole wheat donut.
全麦甜甜圈
A whole wheat donut?
你是指面包圈
You mean a bagel?
不 我是说 一个 全 麦 甜甜圈
No. I mean, a whole, wheat, donut.
好吧 为了更清楚点
So, to be perfectly clear,
我要的是一个全麦甜甜圈
I want a whole wheat donut.
其他的你们随便挑 我不在乎
You can pick the rest, I don't care.
另外 你们不要发甜甜圈 我来发
Oh, and don't pass them out. I'm passing them out.
你们只需要负责买就行了
You are just buying them.
如果你们在开会前发了甜甜圈 你们就被解雇了 懂吗
If you pass them out before the meeting, you are fired. Got it?
- 没问题 - 很好
- Yeah, no problemo. - Good.
我刚刚说了什么
Now what did I tell you?
去买甜甜圈但不要发 不然我们就被解雇了
Get the donuts and don't pass them out, or we are fired.
还有呢
And?
- 还有 你要一个全麦甜甜圈 - 很好
- Oh, and you want a whole wheat donut. - Good.
也许你们确实准备好承担更多责任了
Maybe you are ready for more responsibility.
现在去买甜甜圈吧
Now go get the donuts.
甜甜甜甜甜圈 甜甜甜甜甜圈 甜甜圈
D-d-d-d-donuts! D-d-d-d-donuts, donuts!
甜甜甜甜甜圈 甜甜甜甜-
D-d-d-d-donuts! D-d-d-d--
快去买 不然就炒了你们
Just buy the donuts or you are fired!
糖糖甜甜圈
伙计 来买甜甜圈吧
Aw-yeayuh boy, let's pick some donuts!
等等 还记得本森的嘱咐吗
Wait dude, remember what Benson told us?
请帮我们拿一个全麦甜甜圈
We'd like one whole wheat donut please.
好了 现在我们可以随便挑了
Alright. Now we can pick what we want.
2个这个 5个这个 再来点这个
Let's get two of those! And five of those, and some of those!
等等 那是什么
Wait, what are those?
不行
Uh, no.
那些是意外裹上了双倍糖浆的酥饼
Those are fritters, double glazed by mistake.
双倍糖浆...
Double glazed...
我们买了
We'll take them!
实际上 我准备丢了它们
Actually, I get to throw them out, brah,
因为吃下它们可不安全
because they aren't safe for human consumption.
我们付10块钱
We'll give you ten bucks.
你们要在这吃还是打包
Uhh, you want those here or to-go?
甜甜圈买好咯
Donuts delivered!
这工作可真轻松 一眨眼功夫就完成了
Dude, that job was so easy, we got it done in no time!
没了个错
YEAH WE DID!
想玩一局"鲨鱼超级快打7"吗
Wanna play a round of Super Fight Shark 7?
如果你愿意被我痛扁的话
Only if you feel like losing.
裹着糖浆的小点心
Glazed delights!
你好啊
Well, hello there!
三战两胜
That's two out of three!
我是因为口渴了才输掉第一轮
I only lost the first one because I was thirsty!
随你怎么说 反正你总是口渴
Whatever, you're always thirsty.
你们好你们好你们好 摩迪凯 瑞格比 你们看到这些甜甜圈了吗
Hellohellohello Mordecai and Rigby, did you see that there's donuts here?!
帕布 你是不是吃了一个苹果酥
Pops, did you eat an apple fritter?
怎么了 是 是 我吃了一个
Why, yes, yes I did eat an apple fritter.
本森嘱咐我们不要让任何人偷吃
Benson told us not to let anyone touch those!
天呐 希望我没给你们添麻烦
Oh my, I hope I haven't caused anyone trouble!
别急 帕布
Don't sweat it, Pops.
看
Here.
问题解决了
Problem solved.
本森绝对不会知道帕布偷吃了一个
Benson will never know that Pops ate one.
但我确实吃了一个 尝起来太神奇了
Oh, but I did eat one, it tasted like magic!
在本森发现之前 我们还是把他带出去吧
Let's get him out of here before Benson sees.
这根本没用 他没法停下来
Dude, it's no use, he won't hold still!
我很抱歉 摩迪凯 瑞格比
Oh, I'Whm sorry, Mordecai and Rigby.
但我没法抗拒那些美味的苹果酥 它们实在是太美...
But I couldn't avoid those declicious apple fritters they were positively frittl-
我超爱你们的房间装修 摩迪凯 瑞格比
I like what you did to your room, Mordecai and Rigby!!
帕布 冷静点
Pops, chill.
再过15分钟就开会了
Dude, the meeting starts in fifteen minutes!
我们怎么才能让他在开会前冷静下来
How are we going to calm him down before it starts?!
只能让他精疲力尽了
We have to tire him out.
伙计 这根本不管用
Dude, this isn't working!
过不了几分钟就开会了
We've only got a couple of minutes before the meeting starts
但他还是超兴奋的
and he is still super hyper!
我们带他去找跳跳吧
We've got to take him to Skips.
没错 我以前见过他这样子
Yeah, I've seen this happen to him before.
如果让他吃更多糖 他就安静下来了
He'll just crash if we just give him more sugar.
真的吗 更多糖
Really? More sugar?
你真的确定吗
Are you sure about that?
我有错过吗
Have I ever been wrong?
棒极了棒极了棒极了棒极了
GOOD SHOW GOOD SHOW GOOD SHOW GOOD SHOW!
最好再多给他点
Better give him some more.
棒极了棒极了棒极了棒极了
GOOD SHOW GOOD SHOW GOOD SHOW GOOD SHOW!
什么 为什么说"惨了"
What? Why "Uh-oh"?
他会回来的 对吧
He is coming back, right?
也许不会
Probably not.
什么
WHAT?!
拿个甜甜圈 我们跟上去找他
Grab a donut. We're going in after him.
"另一边"见
See you on the other side.
真好吃
Tasty.
太好了 你们都来了
Oh, hurray! You're all here!
帕布 你恢复正常了
Pops! You're back to normal!
还没有 看看周围
Not yet. Look around.
这是怎么回事
What's going on?
我们现在处于高糖状态
We're on a higher sugar plane.
他们看上去动作很慢 是因为我们动作太快了
They appear to be moving slow because we're moving so fast.
要恢复正常 我们还是需要更多的糖
We still need more sugar before we can crash.
但是苹果酥都被我们吃光了
But we ate all the fritters!
我可以再去买点
Oh, I could buy some more.
就是这个 帕布的钱
That's it! Pops' money!
那肯定含有足够的糖份
That should have enough sugar.
你们要吃了我的钱
We're going to eat my money?
这是恢复正常的唯一办法 帕布
It's the only way to get back to normal, Pops.
我们必须这么做
We HAVE to.
好吧...
Oh... alright.
有麻烦了
We've got a problem.
钱不够分
There's not enough.
你们先走 我另外想办法回去
You guys go ahead. I'll figure a way back.
但跳跳...
But Skips-
没时间争论了 马上就要开会了
No time to argue! The meeting is gonna start in any minute!
就听他的吧
You heard the man!
这是怎么...
What the-
看 是跳跳
Look, it's Skips!
跳跳
Skips!
跳跳 你还...
Skips, are you-
帕布 快回来
Pops, come back!
帕布
POPS!
他在那
There he is.
帕布 你没事吧
Pops, you okay?
伙计 这太不对劲了
Dude, this is all wrong.
为什么这办法不管用
Why isn't this working?!
我想回家
I wanna go home!!!
别担心 帕布 我们会想到办法回去的
Don't worry, Pops, we'll figure something out.
我想我知道方法了
Dude! I think I have an idea!
好吧 那可真吓到我了
Alright. That scares me.
不 伙计 我说真的 如果更多的糖不能让我们恢复
No dude! Seriously, if more sugar doesn't make us crash,
那我们就不要再吃更多的糖了
we need the opposite of sugar!
比如说
Like what?
本森的全麦甜甜圈
Benson's whole wheat donut!
好吧 如果我们要带跳跳一起回去
Alright. If we are going to go back and get Skips,
就得好好分配这个甜甜圈
we'll have to ration this.
办法管用了
Dude, it worked!
怎么回事
What happened?
跳跳 你弄错了
Dude, Skips, you were wrong!
我们需要的是全麦甜甜圈 不是更多糖
The whole wheat donut was what we needed all along, not more sugar!
什..什么
W-what?!
我..我..错了
I-I was...wrong?
事实摆在眼前 跳跳 你错了
In your face, Skips! You were WRONG!
难以置信
Sheesh,
对不起 我..
well I'm sorry I-
错了 彻头彻尾的错了
WRONG, I SAY!! YOU WERE WRONG FULLY WRONG!!
好了 好了 那又能怎么样
Okay, OKAY! What do you expect?!
你们每个礼拜都会丢个不同的问题给我处理
It's like you guys ask me to solve a defferent problem every week!
是呀 是呀
Yeah, yeah.
好了 让我们恢复正常吧
Alright, let's go back to normal.
等等
Wait, dude.
不-好-
Oh, no, bro!
要-去-开-会-了-
Gotta go to the meeting!
他说什么
Uhh, what did he say?
听起来像"腰剧开灰老"
Oh, it sounded like a gound of meat!
不 他要去开会了
No, he is going to the meeting!
时间快到了 去房子那 快
It's about to start! To the house, quick!
开-会-咯--
Meeting time!
我们能赶上
We're gonna make it!
瑞格比 快把甜甜圈放下
Rigby! Put the donuts down!
没有甜甜圈了
There aren't any donuts left!
本森会发飙的...
Benson's not going to like that...
的确
No, he's not.
我们得再跑一趟甜甜圈店
We have to go back to the donut shop.
糖糖甜甜圈
这是怎么...
What the-
公园
放进去了
They're in!
所有人快吃剩下的全麦甜甜圈
Everyone eat the rest of the whole wheat donut!
我-买-了-甜甜圈哦
I've got donuts!
这就是好老板会做的事
Because that's what cool bosses do.
请用
Dig in!
噢...我的头...
Oh... my head...
我不要再吃糖了...
No more sugar...
不吃糖
No sugar?
你们损失大了 老太婆们
You're lost, grandmas.
这样我就能吃更多了
More for me, bro!
你们知道还有谁喜欢狂塞老板给的免费甜甜圈吗
You know who else likes to stuff themselves with their boss's free donuts?
我老妈
My mom!
我老妈 我老妈 我老妈 我老妈
My mom! My mom! My mom my mom!
我老妈
My mom!
我老妈 我老妈 我老妈 我老妈
My mom! My mom! My mom my mom!
我老妈老妈老妈老妈老妈
My mommy mommy mommy mommy mom!
我妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈妈
My mommy mommy mommy mommy moooo!
嘿 我的全麦甜甜圈呢
Hey, where's my whole wheat donut?!